

Profile



Romina Ghaderi



rominaa.ghaderi94@ gmail.com



+46700182173



Brunskogsbacken 70 12371 FARSTA



in linkedin.com/in/rominaghaderi-8b6074232



github.com/romigh94



portfolio-romigh94.vercel. app

Languages

Swedish (Native)



English



Hobbies

- Hang out with friends and family
- Big interest for Web development and Webdesign

Romina Ghaderi

Fullstack Developer

About me

I'm a Fullstack developer from Sweden. During my education I have learned to build and design software with different technologies. It's a big passion for me. I have experience in React, Vue and Node.is etc. I find it easy to understand new technology and I'm a fast learner. I'm also described by others as a girl with great commitment to her work and someone who spreads positive energy.

Education

Frontend development

aug 2021 - jun 2023

Jensen yrkeshögskola, Kista

I have learned to work with: HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, Javascript, React.js, Vue.js, Next.js, Node.js, MongoDB, Git/Github, UX/UI design, Figma, Trello, Heroku, CI/CD pipelines and Docker.

2016 - 2017 Allmän kurs

Södertörns folkhögskola, Solna High school degree

Work experience

Frontend developer

apr 2023 - jun 2023

Les creatives, Stockholm

- I participated in projects and did minor tasks.
- I worked with Vue.js, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS, Node.js and MongoDB.

Frontend developer

nov 2022 - feb 2023

Webbfabriken, Stockholm

• I worked with: HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, Node.js, Next.js and Figma,.

Assistant nurse

2020 - 2021

Vardaga, Stockholm

Assistant nurse

2018 - 2020

Attendo, Stockholm

References

References will be provided after request